Your spot is officially saved and I am so excited.
I know you're going to walk away with a lot of clarity
around your content and what to actually focus on next.
And I can't wait to see what you do with it.
The most important thing that I want you to do right now
is to check your email,
since that's where you'll not only find the workshop details,
but also the free workbook that goes with our session
and even some extra resources to help you get even more
out of our training, like AI prompts for content generation.
But you'll want to go through our training first
just to get the full context for how to use them effectively.
Now, one thing I want to make sure you know
is to try to show up live and stick around till the end
because that's when I'll be sharing
the free Notion content calendar template,
along with a full tutorial that I put together for it.
So that way you can take action immediately
after our session and start planning your content.
And I'm only dropping that link at the end of the session,
so you'll definitely want to be there for that part.
All right, I will see you soon.